If you give these men and ladies wisdom and guidance and encouragement for that great order
that they would know that they were appreciated, I'd thought they'd give them vision
as well as wisdom, all of them, and all of them, and they do, and that the situation
that they make are about how we thank you and we praise you in Christ Jesus Christ, and
holy and we do pray.
Amen.
Please, John, in the pledge.
I'd tell you just to apply the out of the church of America.
And to the word of God, for which it stands, one issue, under God, any of this,
but I think I'd repeat that just as far off.
Thanks again.
Thank you, Peter.
I look forward to this.
Followed in what those guys are for personal appearances, is there any one of the
most important questions to address the council on any of the agenda?
If you're being known, I have a five as Conservatives, Conservatives, Staff, and I am
six through that.
Thank you.
I don't know.
What six through that, six through that, six through that, there are no questions that
have to be 20 minutes and engage in a lot of the full conference, so that's it.
It's not the improvement.
And second, take a roll call for you.
Johnson.
All right.
Forester.
Weston.
All right.
I don't know.
Adam 10 is staff reports, so is your packet available and staff present if there are any questions.
Press the information in your announcements.
I'm full.
I was adjourned.
We have a most good job.
May I ask you a minute.
What are you doing today?
Second.